Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
- Media, 1906-2014
  - 2. Magnetic Tape, 1954-2002
    - Commercial Cassette, 1974-2000
      - New England, 1985; tr-16383; Griner, Clyde; Terra; Vanguard Recording Society (Box 15)
        CT-4
      - Electronic Music: The Pioneers, 1985; tr-16546; Luening, Otto; Ussachevsky, Vladimir; Varèse, Edgard; Babbitt, Milton; Composers Recordings Inc (Box 21)
        ACS 6010
      - Electronic Music: The Pioneers, 1985; tr-16547; Luening, Otto; Ussachevsky, Vladimir; Varèse, Edgard; Babbitt, Milton; Composers Recordings Inc (Box 21)
      - Thank You, 1985; tr-16200; Myggen, Bent; Win Creations (Box 10)
        La Canada, California
      - Lord of the Songs, 1985; tr-16173; Tammy; Another Way Productions (Box 10)
        Asheville, North Carolina
      - Touchboard to Circuit Board, 1986; tr-16157; Chapman, Emmett; Back Yard Records (Box 10)
        BYR-2C
        Los Angeles, California
      - The Velocity of Love, 1986; tr-16673; Ciani, Suzanne; RCA Records (Box 21)
        AMKI-7125
      - Cornerstone, 1986; tr-16161; Lord's Song; Waymark Records (Box 10)
        LS-010
      - The Spirit of Christmas, 1986; tr-16376; Driscoll, Phil; Mighty Horn Records; Benson Records (Box 15)
        CO2308
      - Instrument of Praise, 1986; tr-16153; Driscoll, Phil; The Benson Company, Inc.; Mighty Horn Records (Box 10)
        CO3915
        Nashville, Tennessee
      - Impromptu - Outtakes Vol. I-II, 1987; tr-16356; Berger, Joe (Box 15)
      - Human Interface, 1987; tr-16170; Moraz, Patrick; Capitol Records (Box 10)
        4XT-12558
      - Earthzone, 1987; tr-16179; Pyles, Zon Vern; Synthespan Productions (Box 10)
        Synthespan 0001
        Scottsdale, Arizona
      - Ethereal Shaking Music, 1988; tr-16151; Fairstein, Joel; Apieron Music (Box 10)
        API-1001
      - Safecracker Suite, 1988; tr-16150; Feynman, Richard; Leighton, Ralph (Box 10)
        Pasadena, California
      - Pink Sounds from the Purple Plain, 1988; tr-16670; Parsons, Tom (Box 21)
      - Inside Out, 1989; tr-16285; Hear Here (Box 15)
        HH00127
      - Out There, 1989; tr-16152; Truly Dangerous Swamp Band, The; Hear Here (Box 10)
        HH00143
        Charlotte, North Carolina
      - Catalog and letter accompanying tr-16547, 1992-04-15; Luening, Otto (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Szymanowski: Stabat Mater etc., Rattle, 1994; tr-16183; Szymanowski; Rattle, Simon; EMI (Box 10)
        7243 5 55121 4 7
      - A Perfect Day, 1995; tr-16350; Pearlman, Jon; Permanent Records (Box 15)
        JP-61055
      - Fresh Air with Terry Gross, 2000-02-28; tr-16516; National Public Radio (Box 21)
      - Fresh Air with Terry Gross, 2000-02-28; tr-16517; National Public Radio (Box 21)
      - Travelin' in Style, Undated; tr-16159; Canaanland; Summit (Box 10)
        SR00101
      - From Moog to Mac: The Electronic Music of Herb Deutsch, Undated; tr-16669; Deutsch, Herbert A.; Pulse Concepts (Box 21)
        PC 101
      - XLII, Undated; tr-16310; Horizon Music Group (Box 15)
      - The Way it Oughta Be, Undated; tr-16166; Huffam, Teddy, and the Gems; Pinnacle; Hear Here (Box 10)
        PR00101
      - Guess Where I'm Goin' For Supper, Undated; tr-16158; Parrack, Johnny; Pinnacle (Box 10)
        PR00108
      - Sky High, Undated; tr-16171; Royal City; Pinnacle; Hear Here (Box 10)
        PR-00104
      - Tellus #22: False Phonemes, Undated; tr-16671; Scha, Remko; Wendt, Larry; Reinolt, Brian; Rudolph, Mark; Shields, Alice; Demarinis, Paul; Lansky, Paul; English, Jon; Pomeroy, Jim; Kuivila, Ron; Cage, John; Tellus, The Audiocassette Magazine (Box 21)
        CM1788
    - Non-Commercial Cassette, 1969-2002
      - Kathleen Allen, Undated; tr-16216; Allen, Kathleen (Box 10)
      - Apocalypse Now, 1979; tr-16316; American Zoetrore (Box 15)
      - John Amuedo, Undated; tr-16208; Amuedo, John (Box 10)
        Amuedo, John
      - 4 Songs, Undated; tr-16710; Baltimores, The (Box 20)
      - Ambient, 1996; tr-16700; Bauhs, Brian (Box 20)
      - The In Sound from Way Out, 2002; tr-16395; Becht, Greg (Box 15)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16395, 2002-02-27; Becht, Greg (Box 15, Folder 2)
        Accompanies tr-16395
      - Carols for Christmas (cassette master), Undated; tr-16287; Beecher, Mike (Box 15)
      - The FDSS demo, 1987-01; tr-17137; Belanger, Louis; Lyre Inc. (Box 72)
      - Boulanger: Dissertation, 1987; tr-17139; Belanger, Louis (Box 72)
      - New Directions: Article Sounds, 1987; tr-17138; Belanger, Louis (Box 72)
      - WPLJ-FM ABC New York. Alex Bennett Show with Roger Powell as Guest, 1974-10-10; tr-16269; Bennett, Alex; Powell, Roger (Box 10)
      - Censorship and the Arts - Ken Betsalel Mashburn, Bowen, Undated; tr-16535; Betsalel, Kenneth (Box 21)
      - Ken Bichel, 1987; tr-16288; Bichel, Ken (Box 15)
        Bichel, Ken
      - The Score to 'The Magic Egg', 1985; tr-16537; Boddicker, Michael; Bodifications, Inc. (Box 21)
      - Passing Us By, Undated; tr-16321; Bodrug, Brent (Box 15)
      - Birthday Variations Vol. 1, Undated; tr-16165; Borden, David (Box 10)
      - Borden CD - CPT 5, 6, 7, Undated; tr-16247; Borden, David (Box 10)
      - Dave Borden, 1989-06; tr-16279; Borden, David (Box 15)
      - Dave Borden/ Anatidae, Undated; tr-16258; Borden, David (Box 10)
      - Live at Cornell University and the ABC Café, 1986-05; tr-16164; Borden, David; New Mother Mallard Band, The; Ugly Duckling Consort, The; Earthquack Cassettes (Box 10)
      - Demos of K250 sounds, 1985-10-12; tr-16196; Brigida, Mike (Box 10)
      - Crazy Horse, 1979-1980; tr-16261; Buffalo Philharmonic; Woods, Phil (Box 10)
      - Theremin demo, Undated; tr-16396; Butts, Wes (Box 15)
      - Carlos 2, Undated; tr-16123; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Carlos 3, Undated; tr-16124; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Music from "Catalyst", 1985; tr-16655; Carlos, Wendy (Box 21)
      - Poem for Bali, Himalayan Incantation, 1985; tr-16133; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
        "Dub of Master for Bob and Shirleigh"
      - Secrets of Synthesis, 1986; tr-16129; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Secrets of Synthesis, 1986; tr-16130; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Songs of Distant Earth, 1985; tr-16128; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Wendy 5, Undated; tr-16126; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Wendy 7, Undated; tr-16127; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Wendy Carlos, 1981-02; tr-16121; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Wendy Carlos, 1982-08-22; tr-16122; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Wendy Carlos 4, Undated; tr-16125; Carlos, Wendy (Box 10)
      - Digital Moonscapes, Undated; tr-16317; Carlos, Wendy; Erdenklang; Columbia (Box 15)
        M39340
      - Demo G., Undated; tr-16625; Carlos, Wendy; Kazdin, Andrew; Shepard, Thomas; Kingsley, Gershon; Emerson, Keith; Trythall, Gil; Taylor, Larry (Box 21)
      - Matthew Carlton, Undated; tr-16213; Carlton, Matthew (Box 10)
        Waxahachie, Texas
      - Ause den Tagebuchern, Undated; tr-16254; Chambers, Evan K. (Box 10)
      - Excerpts from Purple Hearts, Metalstorm, Undated; tr-16219; Chang, Gary K. (Box 10)
      - Reckless Night on Board the Bottom Line: A Live Tribute to Raymond Scott, 1996; tr-16702; Chusid, Irwin (Box 20)
      - Music by Saul Consentino, Undated; tr-16658; Consentino, Saul (Box 21)
      - Michael Cough, Undated; tr-16178; Cough, Michael (Box 10)
      - Consequences, 1977; tr-16401-16403; Creme, Lol; Godley, Kevin; Mercury Records; 3 cassettes housed in LP box set-style case (Box 12)
        7299 629, 7299 630, 7299 631
      - Steve Cumming with Robert Moog - "The Morning Program" WRR-FM, Dallas, 1988-11-03; tr-16335; Cumming, Steve; Moog, Robert; WRR-FM (Box 15)
      - Dank, 1996; tr-16198 (Box 10)
      - Megalyra, 1984; tr-16225; Darres, Ivor (Box 10)
        Glendale, California
      - I. Sounds of Just Intonation - Nontraditional Harmony III - Concert of New and Old Music, 1984; tr-16338; David Hill, Ralph (Box 15)
      - II. Sounds of Just Intonation - Nontraditional Harmony III - Concert of New and Old Music, 1984; tr-16339; David Hill, Ralph (Box 15)
      - Mario Davidowsky, 1981-01-30; tr-16113; Davidowsky, Mario (Box 10)
        Davidowsky, Mario
      - News Promotion Package Commercials/ Sci-Fi and Fairy Tale Music, 1980; tr-16352; Davis, Phil (Box 15)
      - Theremin Amsterdam, 1996; tr-16697; De Haas, Polo; Lovsky, Fay (Box 20)
      - Flyers accompanying tr-16697, 1996; De Haas, Polo; Lovsky, Fay (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Last half of conv. with Derocco, 1st half lost, 1989-09-08; tr-16629; Derocco, Paul (Box 21)
      - Tail end of convers. with Paul Derocco, 1989-09-09; tr-16637; Derocco, Paul (Box 21)
      - Electroacoustic Music, 1996-10; tr-16255; Dimitryakova, Julia; Belantsov, Valery (Box 10)
        Moscow, Russia
      - Acid Phisixs Trance Productions, 1996; tr-16711; DJ Phisixs (Box 20)
        1
      - Letter accompanying tr-16711 and tr-16704, 1997-02-19; Cuddihy, David (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Phil Driscoll, sides 1 and 2, 1985-07-15; tr-16217; Driscoll, Phil (Box 10)
      - Phil Driscoll, sides 3 and 4, 1985-07-15; tr-16218; Driscoll, Phil (Box 10)
      - Robert Dunning and Tucker Cooke - talking about Gerry Wubben's Exhibit, Undated; tr-16211; Dunning, Robert; Cooke, Tucker (Box 10)
      - Scenes from an Exhibition, 1990-04; tr-16284; Dunnington, Stephen; Ravetto, Susan; Bakan, Jonathan; Haynes, Houston (Box 15)
      - Lullabye for Gregory in Canada, Undated; tr-16512; Electronic Art Ensemble (Box 15)
      - The Human Animal, Undated; tr-16249; Elliott, Bill (Box 10)
      - Keith Emerson interview w Ray Hammond, London, 1975-04-28; tr-16301; Emerson, Keith; Hammond, Ray (Box 15)
      - Keith Emerson and Bob Moog, 1975-05-09; tr-16149; Emerson, Keith; Moog, Robert (Box 10)
      - ELP Concert A, 1973-12-07; tr-16119; Emerson, Lake and Palmer (Box 10)
      - ELP Concert B, 1973-12-07; tr-16120; Emerson, Lake and Palmer (Box 10)
      - Eric Ross Ensemble V2, 1994; tr-16162; Eric Ross Ensemble (Box 10)
      - Electronic Music Album, Undated; tr-16349; Estrin, Robert (Box 15)
        Bloomington, Indiana
      - Synergy Metropolitan Suite, 1987-03-15; tr-16244; Fast, Larry (Box 10)
        SYNCO 204
      - Elliot the Old Soul, Undated; tr-16278; Fischer, William (Box 10)
      - Michael Fremer, first cassette, 1981-08-13; tr-16114; Fremer, Michael (Box 10)
        Fremer, Michael
      - Michael Fremer, second cassette, 1981-08-04; tr-16115; Fremer, Michael (Box 10)
      - Dominic Frontiere demo, Undated; tr-16207; Frontiere, Dominic (Box 10)
      - Definition of Studio Interface, 1981-10-31; tr-16275; Fryer, Terry (Box 10)
      - The Last Temptation of Christ, Undated; tr-16666; Gabriel, Peter (Box 21)
      - Moog Concert, 2000; tr-16674; Galper, Hal; Swangen, Chris (Box 21)
      - Spinning on Air- WNYC - Theremin, 1993-05-25; tr-16391; Garland, David; WNYC (Box 15)
      - Spinning on Air- WNYC - Theremin, 1993-05-25; tr-16392; Garland, David; WNYC (Box 15)
      - Spinning on Air- WNYC - Theremin, 1993-05-25; tr-16393; Garland, David; WNYC (Box 15)
      - Spinning on Air- WNYC - Theremin, 1993-05-25; tr-16394; Garland, David; WNYC (Box 15)
      - Spinning on Air- WNYC - Theremin, 1993-05-25; tr-16250; Garland, David; WNYC (Box 10)
      - Spinning on Air- WNYC - Theremin, 1993-05-25; tr-16542; Garland, David; WNYC (Box 21)
      - Spinning on Air- WNYC - Theremin, 1993-05-25; tr-16712; Garland, David; WNYC (Box 20)
      - Columbia University Columputer Music, 1989; tr-16654; Garton, Brad (Box 21)
      - Heat, 1985; tr-16283; Gilman, Paul (Box 15)
      - Live at Symphony Hall, 1985; tr-16167; Gilman, Paul (Box 10)
      - The Giraffe Had a Voice, 1998; tr-16387; Giraffe Had a Voice, The (Box 15)
      - Powaqqatsi, Undated; tr-16292; Glass, Philip; Elektra; Nonesuch (Box 15)
        9-79192-2
      - KB Soundsheet: Heckert and RBB; Ralph Grierson - "Sometimes Not Always", 1986-05; tr-16238; Grierson, Ralph (Box 10)
      - Margaret Bosley Theremin 1963, Undated; tr-16545; Gustin, Gary (Box 21)
      - Album Myself, 1988; tr-17141; Hamilton, Dick (Box 72)
      - Orchestration for Synthesizer, 1988; tr-17140; Hamilton, Dick (Box 72)
      - Letter accompanying tr-17140-17141, 1988-01-11; Hamilton, Dick (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Jan Hammer, Undated; tr-16298; Hammer, Jan (Box 15)
      - Eddie Harris/ Leon Russel/ Steppen Wolf, 1973-07-10; tr-16685; Harris, Eddie; Russell, Leon; Steppenwolf (Box 21)
      - Digital Orchestrations, Undated; tr-16650; Heckert, Paul (Box 21)
      - Keyboard - Live!, 1988; tr-16623; Heckert, Paul (Box 21)
      - Paul Heckert, Undated; tr-16665; Heckert, Paul (Box 21)
      - Synthesizer demo, 1989-03; tr-16312; Heckert, Paul (Box 15)
      - Chord transitions contrasted for Bob Moog/ Harmony and number demo, 1985-04-02-1985-12; tr-16615; Hill, Ralph David (Box 21)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16615, 1985-12-27; Hill, Ralph David (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Lifestyle Report - "North American New Music Festival", 1991-04-19; tr-16141; Hughes, Rebekkah; Moog, Robert (Box 10)
      - Live D.A.T. Mix, 1997-01; tr-16704; IndiaDrop (Box 20)
      - Denny Jaeger and Michel Rubini's New Synclavier II Demo, Undated; tr-16544; Jaeger, Denny; Rubini, Michel (Box 21)
      - Melody for Piano and Theremin, 1929 - Joseph Schillinger, 1992-05-27; tr-16668; James, Dennis; Kuterns, Jerome (Box 21)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16668, 1992-05-27; James, Dennis; Kuterns, Jerome (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - The Arrangements for a Display and an Orchestra, 1996; tr-16181; Jivaikin, Paul (Box 10)
      - Love Letters Original Motion Picture Score, Undated; tr-16205; Jones, Ralph (Box 10)
      - Aliquando Fidelis, 1989-10-11; tr-16257; Kirby, Wayne (Box 10)
      - Aliquando Fiedlis, 1989; tr-16252; Kirby, Wayne (Box 10)
      - Sons of Another Planet, 1996; tr-16351; Kirby, Wayne; Olson, Greg (Box 15)
      - Darlene Koldenhoven master demo, 1984; tr-16380; Koldenhoven, Darlene (Box 15)
      - Voice of Theremin/ First Airphonic Suite, Undated; tr-16245; Komorov, Vladimir; Schillinger, Joseph (Box 10)
      - Demo E - East European, Undated; tr-16645; Kotonski, Wlodzimerz; Dobrowolski, Amorzes; Schaeffer, Bogustaw; Rudnik, Eugeniusz; Nemtin, A.; Kreichi, S. (Box 21)
      - CZ-101 Demonstration, Undated; tr-16172; Kovarsky, Jerry (Box 10)
      - Kraftwek - Autobahn, Florian/ Speech Synthesizer Votrax demo tape, Undated; tr-16509; Kraftwerk (Box 15)
      - The Electronic Art Ensemble, 1980-06-15; tr-16111; Kramer, Gregory (Box 10)
      - Music of the Thirteen Moons, 1995; tr-16618; Kubie, Chris (Box 21)
      - Press kit accompanying tr-16618, 1995-08; Kubie, Chris (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Idle Chatter/Guy's Harp, Undated; tr-16657; Lansky, Paul (Box 21)
      - Paul Lansky examples (See letter of May 23, '88), Undated; tr-16136; Lansky, Paul (Box 10)
      - Paul Lehrman, Undated; tr-16289; Lehrman, Paul (Box 15)
        Lehrman, Paul
      - The Celtic Macintosh, 1986; tr-16182; Lehrman, Paul D. (Box 10)
        Cambridge, Massachusetts
      - Genzmer/Fuleihan: Early Electronic Music, 1997-09; tr-16705; Lester, Charlie (Box 20)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16705, 1997-09; Lester, Charlie (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Demo tape, 1976-12; tr-16277; Lorber, Jeff (Box 10)
        Vancouver, Washington
      - De Iljsbreker, 1995; tr-16701; Lovsky, Fay (Box 20)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16701, 1995-12-19; Lovsky, Fay (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Luenning, Undated; tr-16118; Luening, Otto (Box 10)
      - Electronic composition "Moog Liberator" - 4 track stereo recording, Undated; tr-16135; Marzewski, Dale (Box 10)
      - Expo compilation, 1986; tr-16290; McGuinness, Timothy (Box 15)
      - Timothy McGuinness, 1985; tr-16291; McGuinness, Timothy (Box 15)
      - BBC Radio 2 Theremin: "Look No Hands!", 1996-06; tr-16706; McKenovick, Dougie (Box 20)
      - Paul Tanner Collection: Electro-Theremin, 1997; tr-17142; Miller, David (Box 72)
      - Concertare, Undated; tr-16631; Miller, Harvey H. (Box 21)
      - Arts 310 project, 1990; tr-16286; Molina, Mimi; Smith, Cena; Austin, Kenny (Box 15)
      - Interview between R. Moog and R. Sherman on WXQR - first hour, 1974-09-13; tr-16147; Moog, Robert; WXQR (Box 10)
      - Interview between R. Moog and R. Sherman on WXQR - second hour, 1974-09-13; tr-16148; Moog, Robert; WXQR (Box 10)
      - Bourges, 1989; tr-16142; Moog, Robert (Box 10)
      - Fairlight demo, Undated; tr-16223; Moog, Robert (Box 10)
      - Moog, Abbott and Lewis - Asheville Art Museum, 1980-11-23; tr-16138; Moog, Robert (Box 10)
      - Synthesis: Old and New Sounds - Robert Moog - MENC Biennial Conference - Phoenix, AZ, 1998-04; tr-16139; Moog, Robert (Box 10)
        Phoenix, Arizona
      - CKMS Radio interview (Moog), Undated; tr-16397; Moog, Robert; Rucki, Eva; KMS-FM (Box 15)
        Kitchener, Ontario
      - Postcard accompanying tr-16397, Undated; Rucki, Eva (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - American Routes with Nick Spitzer, Tape 1, 2000-12-06; tr-16398; Moog, Robert; Spitzer, Nick (Box 15)
        Includes note from Spitzer to Moog and playlist for episode.
      - American Routes with Nick Spitzer, Tape 2, 2000-12-06; tr-16399; Moog, Robert; Spitzer, Nick (Box 15)
      - Card and playlist accompanying tr-16398-16399, 2000-12-06; Spitzer, Nick (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Bob Moog interviewing Vladimir Ussachevsky, tape 1, 1981-01-22; tr-16341; Moog, Robert; Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Box 15)
      - Bob Moog interviewing Vladimir Ussachevsky, tape 2, 1981-01-22; tr-16342; Moog, Robert; Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Box 15)
      - Bob Moog interviewing Vladimir Ussachevsky, Tape 3, 1981-01-22; tr-16343; Moog, Robert; Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Box 15)
      - Patrick Moraz - I - Side A, Undated; tr-16582; Moraz, Patrick (Box 21)
      - Demo tape, Undated; tr-16639; Morgan, Glen E. (Box 21)
      - Fred Moyer interview, tape 1A, 1B, 1985-05-19; tr-16215; Moyer, Fred (Box 10)
      - Musical Saw, Theremin, Undated; tr-16699; Muller, Eric (Box 20)
      - Michael Newman and Laura Oltman - second generation dub, Undated; tr-16315; Newman, Michael; Oltman, Laura (Box 15)
      - Drums of Passion - Dance to the Beat of my Drum, Undated; tr-16374; Olatunji, Babatunde (Box 15)
      - Improvisation #5 for Electronic Percussion Solo, 1997; tr-16696; Ovens, Doug (Box 20)
      - Tape of Moog Sounds for Robert Moog, 1996; tr-16703; Petkovic, John (Box 20)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16703, 1996-04-10; Petkovic, John (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - The Emerald Tablet/ Mad Coyote, Undated; tr-16274; Powell, Roger (Box 10)
      - Short Fantasy for Theremin, Piano, and Orchestra, Undated; tr-16707; Pringle, Peter (Box 20)
      - Project Pimento, Undated; tr-16390 (Box 15)
      - A Study in Fives (2 versions), Undated; tr-16325; Rapoport, Paul (Box 15)
      - A Christmas Collection, 1990; tr-16281; Ravetto, Susan; RPM Productions (Box 15)
      - Micromoog demo, 1977; tr-16144; Raynor, J. (Box 10)
      - Minimoog demo, 1977; tr-16143; Raynor, J. (Box 10)
      - Polymoog demo, 1977; tr-16146; Raynor, J. (Box 10)
      - Taurus and accessories demo, 1977; tr-16145; Raynor, J. (Box 10)
      - Never Alone, Undated; tr-16389; Renton, Keith (Box 15)
        Surrey, United Kingdom
      - Rhea Micromoog demo, 1976-06; tr-16134; Rhea, Tom (Box 10)
      - T. Rhea's slides, Undated; tr-16231; Rhea, Tom (Box 10)
      - To Bob Moog - General Information on Fair, 1976; tr-16676; Rhea, Tom (Box 21)
      - To Bob Moog - Special Information ref. Roland Modular System, 1976; tr-16677; Rhea, Tom (Box 21)
      - Roland and Martinetta brochures accompanying tr-16676-16677, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - The Wizard of Oz, Undated; tr-16268; Rigmann, Kurt (Box 10)
      - Clara Rockmore, Undated; tr-16270; Rockmore, Clara (Box 10)
      - Clara Rockmore, Undated; tr-16540; Rockmore, Clara (Box 21)
      - Clara Rockmore unreleased recordings (copy from DAT), Undated; tr-16513; Rockmore, Clara (Box 21)
      - Clara Rockmore WQXR, 1977-11-14; tr-16538; Rockmore, Clara (Box 21)
      - Phone Interview with Clara Rockmore, 1977-10; tr-16302; Rockmore, Clara (Box 15)
      - Talk with Clara Rockmore, 1974-10-19; tr-16263; Rockmore, Clara (Box 10)
      - The Art of the Theremin, 1987-10; tr-16248; Rockmore, Clara (Box 10)
      - Music from a Window in the Passage, 1991; tr-16529; Rona, Jeff (Box 21)
      - Jordan Rudes, Undated; tr-16648; Rudes, Jordan (Box 21)
      - Oskar Sala, 1989-06-15; tr-16311; Sala, Oskar (Box 15)
        Sala, Oskar
      - Gunther Schuller, Undated; tr-16322; Schuller, Gunther (Box 15)
        Schuller, Gunther
      - Raymond Scott, Undated; tr-16530; Scott, Raymond (Box 21)
      - Raymond Scott: Lecture on Electronic Music in Radio and Television, Undated; tr-16528; Scott, Raymond (Box 21)
      - Jamshied Sharifi, 1987-12; tr-16371; Sharifi, Jamshied (Box 15)
        Sharifi, Jamshied
      - Theremin Solos of the 30's, Undated; tr-16510; Shewell, H. Lennington; Hoffman, Samuel (Box 15)
      - Chroma/Apple Demo - Fender Musical Instruments, 1983-05-20; tr-16617; Shykun, John C.; Smith, Mark; CBS Musical Instruments (Box 21)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16617, 1983-05-20; Shykun, John C. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Electronic Music from the Rainbow Isle, 1978; tr-16160; Slepian, Don (Box 10)
        Murray Hill, New Jersey
      - Pril Smiley, 1981-01-21; tr-16272; Smiley, Phil (Box 10)
      - SolarX, Defective Records, Undated; tr-16253; SolarX; Belavkin, Roman (Box 10)
      - Transformations, 1990-09-18; tr-16667; Sphinx Holotronic (Box 21)
      - Letter accompanying tr-16667, 1992-07-30; Sphinx Holotronic (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Music Mouse Demonstration Music, Fall '90; tr-16627; Spiegel, Laurie (Box 21)
      - The Expanding Universe, Undated; tr-16628; Spiegel, Laurie (Box 21)
      - Media Musics (Selected Sound), Undated; tr-16273; Studio Funk Electronic Sound Prod. (Box 10)
      - Theremin, Undated; tr-16708; Sussman (Box 20)
      - A Demonstration Tape of the Synthesizer Orchestra, 1977-05; tr-16646; Suzuki, Hiroshi; Synthesizer Orchestra of Akashi Junior High School, The (Box 21)
      - Synthesizer Orchestra, 1974; tr-16222; Suzuki, Hiroshi; Synthesizer Orchestra of Akashi Junior High School, The (Box 10)
      - Badger III, 1983; tr-16251; Swansen, Chris (Box 10)
      - Chris Swansen, tape 2, Undated; tr-16340; Swansen, Chris (Box 15)
      - Fire, Undated; tr-16175; System 7; Big Life Records (Box 10)
        London, United Kingdom
      - Water Album, Undated; tr-16174; System 7; Big Life Records (Box 10)
      - The Referee Has Vanished, The Parthenon I, Fantasia, 1982; tr-16229; Tamul, Jack; Mathews, R. (Box 10)
      - Music for Wind Symphony Orchestra, 1989-10; tr-16220; Tcherepnin, Ivan (Box 10)
      - Concerto for Two Continents (MIDI runthrough only), Undated; tr-16626; Tcherepnine, Ivan (Box 21)
      - Ali Baba's Tahini, Undated; tr-16698; Ultragroove (Box 20)
      - Ussachevsky #1, 1981-01-22; tr-16201; Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Box 10)
      - Ussachevsky #3, 1981-01-23; tr-16203; Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Box 10)
      - Ussachevsky 2, 1981-01-23; tr-16202; Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Box 10)
      - Ecuatorial; Piece for Tape Recorder; The Wild Bull; Pictures at an Exhibition, Undated; tr-16539; Varèse, Edgard; Ussachevsky, Vladimir; Subotnick, Morton (Box 21)
      - Order Odonata Volume 1, Undated; tr-16176; Various Artists (Box 10)
      - The Art of Noise: 2 Wondrous Stories, 1994-11-12; tr-16386; Wakeman, Rick; BBC North (Box 15)
      - Six Wives/ Journey, 1974-10-02; tr-16262; Wakeman, Rick (Box 10)
        Rochester, New York
      - Demo C - Risset, Undated; tr-16638; Weiss; Reuther; Risset, Jean-Claude; Carlos, Wendy; Erb, Donald; Drews (Box 21)
      - Audio letter cassette from Reid Welch, Undated; tr-16709; Welch, Reid (Box 20)
      - The Phantom Zone, 1986; tr-16155; Xisle; Lights Out Recordings (Box 10)